worldfriends.com 2018-05-19

# WorldFriends :. Member Services

### Privacy Policy

Meta4 Networks ("WorldFriends") respects the privacy of our users and has developed this Privacy Policy to demonstrate its commitment to protecting your privacy. This Privacy Policy is intended to describe for you, as an individual who is a user of WorldFriends, the information we collect, how that information may be used, and with whom it may be shared.

We encourage you to read this Privacy Policy carefully when using our website or services or transacting business with us. By using our website, you are accepting the practices described in this Privacy Policy. 

WorldFriends cares deeply about online privacy. If you have any questions concerning this privacy policy, contact us. This Privacy Policy was last updated on January 7, 2011. 

#### Persons Under the Age of 18

WorldFriends does not knowingly collect or maintain personally identifiable information or non-personally-identifiable information on the site from persons under 18 years of age, and no part of the site is directed to persons under 18. If you are under 18 years of age, then please do not use or access the site or the services at any time or in any manner. If WorldFriends learns that personally identifiable information of persons under 18 years of age has been collected on the site, then WorldFriends will take the appropriate steps to delete this information.

#### Information We May Collect

We may collect and process the following information about you: 

  * Information that you provide by filling in forms on our service (including your personal details, contact details and other profile information you submit when you create a membership profile). We may also collect information when you voluntarily complete customer surveys, provide feedback and participate in competitions.
  * If you contact us, we may keep a record of that correspondence.
  * Details of transactions you carry out through our service, including any information we require to provide any products or services that you order from us. 
  * Website usage information is also collected using cookies.

Visitors to our service whose personal data have been collected have rights to access the same, mandate corrections, and ascertain our policies and practices with regard to such data. Our visitors should feel free to exercise any of these rights by contacting us directly: Data Protection Officer, Email: [csos@meta4-group.com](mailto:csos@meta4-group.com).

#### Information Others May Collect

We may allow third-parties, including our authorized service providers, advertising companies, and ad networks, to display advertisements on our service. By activating a link (such as a banner of an advertiser), you are leaving our service and if you subsequently provide information, we have no control over its use. This privacy policy does not address the information practices of any of those other websites or advertisers, and WorldFriends disclaims all liability with respect to how they may use any such information.

#### How We May Use Information We Collect

We use the information we collect from you in the following ways: 

  * To manage your user account with us (including notifying you of any compatible matches, tips, announcements, updates, or promotions).
  * To help personalize your returning visits to the service.
  * To provide you with information, products or services that you request from us or which we feel may interest you, where you have consented to be contacted for such purposes.
  * To provide you with customer support.
  * To notify you about changes or new functionalities of the service.
  * To carry out market analysis and research.
  * To help us improve the structure, layout and usability of the service.
  * To ensure that you are complying with our policies.

#### With Whom We May Share Information We Collect

We may share information about you with third parties that we engage to help us in certain areas, such as processing payments for services you order from us. However, we will control and be responsible for the use of your information by these third parties. 

We may also disclose certain information to partner companies with whom we work in order to provide our members with services such as Email and Chat. In order to provide these services, we must disclose certain information to our partners including your WorldFriends username and email address. 

We may also provide information about you to other users of the service as reasonably required in order to provide services such as MatchMail. 

Other companies may help sponsor promotions, contests and sweepstakes running on WorldFriends. These companies may choose to collect personal information from you. If you do not wish for your information collected by these sponsors, you can decide not to participate in the promotion, contest or sweepstakes. We have no control over how they may use any such information and WorldFriends disclaims all liability with respect to the same. 

#### Cookies

In our effort to provide you services customized to your interests, we may use cookies to keep and sometimes track information about you. A cookie is a small piece of data that is sent to your browser from a Web server and stored on your computer's hard drive. 

We may use cookies to: 

  * access your account information (stored on our computers) in order to deliver better and more personalized services; 
  * estimate our audience size for our advertisers; 
  * to track the number of entries in our promotions, sweepstakes and contests; 
  * to identify which areas of our service you have visited. 

Cookies are stored typically for 24 hours, or indefinitely if you select “Remember Me” when you sign in to our service.

You may delete or disable cookies by changing your browser settings (Click “Help” in the toolbar of most browsers for instructions). If you do so, some of the features and services of our website may not function properly. Advertisers on our service may use their own cookies, and this privacy policy does not cover how these companies use them.

#### Users in China

For users in China, you agree that WorldFriends may disclose any information, including your name and other information, if it believes in good faith that such action is reasonably necessary to comply with applicable laws and lawful government requests, to operate its systems properly or to protect itself and its members.

#### Changes to our Privacy Policy

We keep our privacy policy under regular review and will post any changes to it on this page. We encourage you to regularly review our privacy policy to make sure you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it and under what circumstances, if any, we may share it with other parties.

#### How to Contact Us

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy or our information-handling practices, or if you would like to request information about our disclosure of personal information to third parties for their direct marketing purposes, please contact us by email or postal mail below:

Privacy Officer   
Meta4 Networks   
801, Millennium Trade Center   
56 Kwai Cheong Road   
Hong Kong   

Meta4 Networks is a service powered, hosted and maintained by Meta4 Group (GLOBAL) S.A. and its subsidiary, including but not limited to Meta4 Group (HK) Limited, Meta4 Group KK and WorldFriends (Global) S.A.R.L. ([http://www.meta4-group.com](http://www.meta4-group.com/)).
